RG 005:038, Office of the Governor: Lowell P. Weicker, Jr. (1991-1995)
Connecticut State Library
- Series 2. Press Files, 1991-1994; 1995-031
  - Old State House construction to begin thanks to state grant, 1992 September 25 (Box 2, Folder 197)
  - Judge Barry R. Schaller nominated to Appellate Court, 1992 September 30 (Box 2, Folder 198)
  - Gov. Weicker unveils urban lending program for five cities, 1992 September 30 (Box 2, Folder 199)
  - Copies of newspaper articles on Connecticut National Guard, 1992 September 30 (Box 2, Folder 200)
  - Connecticut launches out-of-state marketing campaign, 1992 September (Box 2, Folder 201)
  - Gov. Weicker names Charles Howard to Judicial Selection Committee, 1992 October 1 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Gov. Weicker announces grants to cities and towns for State Drug Law Enforcement Program, 1992 October 1 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - State joins in $29 million package to keep Whalers hockey team in Hartford, 1992 October 1 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Special Olympics traveling exhibit, 1992 October 6-10 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Care & Share kickoff, 1992 October 15 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Gov. Weicker announces relocation of medical products firm to Shelton, 1992 October 15 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Prototype & Plastic Mold Co., 1992 October 21 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Gov. Weicker endorsement for President, 1992 October 21 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Stafford Springs mill, 1992 October 21 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Gov. Weicker named National Multiple Sclerosis Society Governor of the Year, 1992 October 29 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Gov. Weicker appoints three to Connecticut Innovations, Inc., 1992 November 6 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Nutmeg Scholarships, 1992 November 12 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Gov. Weicker makes appointments to CADAC and University Board, 1992 November 13 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Gov. Weicker, Commissioner Scherer announce small cities grants of $7.1 million to 17 communities, 1992 November 13 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Gov. Weicker's letter to William Cibes regarding reduction of allotments to agencies, 1992 November 18 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - William Cibes letter to Gov. Weicker on 1992-1993 deficit, 1992 November 18 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Gov. Weicker appoints pair to Judicial selection panel, 1992 November 19 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Dorothy W. Bush condolences, 1992 November 20 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Projected state budged deficit for 1992-1993 memo to agency heads, 1992 November 20 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Gov. Weicker announces state approval for two more insurance companies to sell state-endorsed long-term care policies, 1992 November 23 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Reward letter for Tania Ramsey and Carmen Fagan letters, 1992 November 23 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Gov. Weicker announces appointments to Judicial Review Council, 1992 November 27 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Gov. Weicker appoints Cynthia Matthews Commissioner on Aging, 1992 December 3 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Gov. Weicker names Edgar Beckham as Chairman of the State Board of Education, 1992 December 4 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Gov. Weicker joins the Board of Directors of Americans for Medical Progress, 1992 December 7 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Gov. Weicker calls Saturday election to fill 29th District State Senate vacancy, 1992 December 8 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Fleet Bank selects Connecticut for consumer loan underwriting operation, 1992 December 9 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Governor nominates four Superior Court judges, 1992 December 12 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Letter to President Bush regarding FEMA monies and back-up information, 1992 December 15 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Gov. Weicker applauds Presidential decision granting disaster relief to Connecticut, 1992 December 17 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Disaster assistance efforts move forward, 1992 December 18 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Gov. Weicker opens new Bridgeport office, 1992 December 18 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Gov. Weicker asks for cleanup cost waiver for Cities of Bridgeport and West Haven, 1992 December 23 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Rep. Douglas Mintz to be nominated as judge, 1992 December 23 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Gov.Weicker names members to Intergovernmental Commission, 1992 December 30 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Municipal governments in Middlesex County eligible for disaster aid, 1992 December 31 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Gov. Weicker's New Year message, 1992 December (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Special election for House and Senate seats, 1993 January 5 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - State of the State, 1993 January 6 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Gov. Weicker appoints Richard Treibick of Greenwich as University of Connecticut trustee, 1993 January 8 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - State and Mashantucket Pequot tribe reach agreement on annual payments, 1993 January 13 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Decision made on downtown location for Housatonic Community College site in Bridgeport, 1993 January 13 (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Gov. Weicker nominates Ellen A. Peters for reappointment to 8 year term as Chief Justice, 1993 January 15 (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Residence tour invitation, 1993 January 19 (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - Gov. Weicker nominates Richard Palmer as justice to the Connecticut Supreme Court, 1993 January 21 (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - Reward letter for murder of Joseph Kulikowski, 1993 January 21 (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - Bond Commission authorizations, 1993 January 22 (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - Gov. Weicker appoints A. Searle Field as Chief of Staff, 1993 January 25 (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - Letter to Sen. Larson from Gov. Weicker regarding memorandum of understanding with Mashantucket Pequot tribe, 1993 January 25 (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - Reorganization plan presented to General Assembly, 1993 January 28 (Box 3, Folder 50)
  - Bills signed, 1993 January 28 (Box 3, Folder 51)
  - Welfare reform, 1993 January 31 (Box 3, Folder 52)
  - Gov. Weicker's accomplishments, 1991-1993 (Box 3, Folder 53)
  - Summary of siginificant spending reductions program changes, 1993-1994 (Box 3, Folder 54)
  - Gov. Weicker budget message, 1993 February 3 (Box 3, Folder 55)
  - Gov.Weicker 1994 budget press release, 1993 February 3 (Box 3, Folder 56)
  - Gov. Weicker names Thomas J. Dudchik as deputy chief of staff, 1993 February 4 (Box 3, Folder 57)
  - Dept. of Environmental Protection program reductions 1994, the proposed Environment Fund Bottle Bill, 1993 February 5 (Box 3, Folder 58)
  - Statement from Office of the Governor on allegations of discrimination, 1993 February 9 (Box 3, Folder 59)
  - Gov. Weicker nominates Tom Gerety to State Board of Education, 1993 February 10 (Box 3, Folder 60)
  - Reward letter for murder of Susan Bova, 1993 February 11 (Box 3, Folder 61)
  - Reward letter for murder of John Rooney, 1993 February 11 (Box 3, Folder 62)
  - Ruth L. Pulda assists sexual harassment investigation, 1993 February 17 (Box 3, Folder 63)
  - Letter to Clifton Leonhardt on Cablevision, 1993 February 17 (Box 3, Folder 64)
  - Gov. Weicker announces funding for initiative to examine statewide treatment services for people addicted to alcohol and drugs, 1993 February 18 (Box 3, Folder 65)
  - Veto message for H.B. 6906, income tax, 1993 February 18 (Box 3, Folder 66)
  - Home mortgage program for first time buyers, 1993 February 22 (Box 3, Folder 67)
  - List of judges swearing-in, 1993 February 24 (Box 3, Folder 68)
  - Clinton economic stimulus spending package estimated impace on Connecticut, 1993 February 25 (Box 3, Folder 69)
  - State loans manufacturer $500,000 to develop environmentally friendly cooling system, 1993 February 26 (Box 3, Folder 70)
  - $4.6 million earmarked by State for economic development project, 1993 February 26 (Box 3, Folder 71)
  - Local human service projects to receive state funding, 1993 February 26 (Box 3, Folder 72)
  - Press releases on Bond Commission meeting, 1993 February 26 (Box 3, Folder 73)
  - Local human services projects to receive state funding, 1993 February 26 (Box 3, Folder 74)
  - Gov. Weicker appoints Julie Belaga to Connecticut Development Authority, 1993 March 1 (Box 3, Folder 75)
  - Lt. Gov. Eunice S. Groark testimony to Education Committee, 1993 March 5 (Box 3, Folder 76)
  - Gov. Weicker comments at presentation of University Medal to William C. Steeve, 1993 March 10 (Box 3, Folder 77)
  - Reward letter in connection with Stamford High School fines, 1993 March 10 (Box 3, Folder 78)
  - Storm Josh press releases, 1993 March 12-14 (Box 3, Folder 79)
  - Gov. Weicker address to Education Committee, 1993 March 12 (Box 3, Folder 80)
  - Gov. Weicker asks for U.S. aid for snow removal on emergency routes, 1993 March 15 (Box 3, Folder 81-82)
  - State assists East Lyme firm's effort to diversity with $1.75 million package, 1993 March 15 (Box 3, Folder 83)
  - Gov. Weicker announces emergency aid approved by White House for storm, 1993 March 16 (Box 3, Folder 84)
  - Gov. Weicker statement on Bill 7263 AAC penalty and interest on personal income tax, 1993 March 17 (Box 3, Folder 85)
  - Gov. Weicker announces municipal briefing schedule for U.S. storm aid, 1993 March 17 (Box 3, Folder 86)
  - Gov. Weicker to attend Special Olympics, trip to Salzburg sets stage for Connecticut, 1993 March 17 (Box 3, Folder 87)
  - Bills signed, 1993 March 18 (Box 3, Folder 88)
  - Correction of victim name in reward letter from John Rooney to Robert Rooney, 1993 March 19 (Box 3, Folder 89)
  - Marian Wright Edelman to speak on fighting child poverty, 1993 March 22 (Box 3, Folder 90)
  - Bills signed, 1993 March 24 (Box 3, Folder 91)
  - Connecticut makes offer to Texas, seeks to join compact for low-level radioactive waste disposal, 1993 March 29 (Box 3, Folder 92)
  - Bills signed, 1993 March 31 (Box 3, Folder 93)
  - Bills signed, 1993 April 1 (Box 3, Folder 94)
  - Local human service projects to receive state funding, Bond Commission meeting, 1993 April 2 (Box 3, Folder 95)
  - $4.1 million authorized for state economic development project, Bond Commission, 1993 April 2 (Box 3, Folder 96)
  - Final report on allegations of sexual harassment in the State, 1993 April 2 (Box 3, Folder 97)
  - Gov. Weicker nominates two to Superior Court, also nominates Justice Callahan for reappointment to Supreme Court, 1993 April 5 (Box 3, Folder 98)
  - Bills signed, 1993 April 7 (Box 3, Folder 99)
  - Gov. Weicker statement about Marian Anderson, 1993 April 8 (Box 3, Folder 100)
  - Gov. Weicker nominates Craig E. Toensing to Board of Education, 1993 April 12 (Box 3, Folder 101)
  - Gov. Weicker proposes moving State Police barracks of Troop G to Bridgeport, 1993 April 14 (Box 3, Folder 102)
  - Gov. Weicker statement regarding Pratt & Whitney, 1993 April 14 (Box 3, Folder 103)
  - Statement on meeting with Pratt & Whitney, Office of Policy and Management, and Economic Development, 1993 April 15 (Box 3, Folder 104)
  - Larry Halloran testimony before the Finance, Revenue and Bonding Committee, 1993 April 15 (Box 3, Folder 105)
  - Bills signed, 1993 April 15 (Box 3, Folder 106)
  - Gov. Weicker statement on personal income tax for 1992, 1993 April 16 (Box 3, Folder 107)
  - Gov. Weicker announces formation of commission on future of libraries, 1993 April 19 (Box 3, Folder 108)
  - Bills signed, 1993 April 20 (Box 3, Folder 109)
  - Letter to General Assembly regarding casinos, 1993 April 21 (Box 3, Folder 110)
  - Bills signed, 1993 April 21 (Box 3, Folder 111)
  - Bills signed, 1993 April 22 (Box 3, Folder 112)
  - Gov. Weicker announces state jumps seven places in economic ranking, 1993 April 22 (Box 3, Folder 113)
  - Bond Commission economic development initiatives, 1993 April 23 (Box 3, Folder 114)
  - $3 million in Yankee Ingenuity grants to universities approved by Bond Commission, 1993 April 23 (Box 3, Folder 115)
  - New Wallingford child care center to receive state funding, Bond Commission meeting, 1993 April 23 (Box 3, Folder 116)
  - Bond Commission housing initiatives, $23.5 million, 1993 April 23 (Box 3, Folder 117)
  - Dept. of Environmental Protection waste water treatment plants, Bond Commission meeting, 1993 April 23 (Box 3, Folder 118)
  - Bills signed, 1993 April 23 (Box 3, Folder 119)
  - Gov. Weicker names Cathy Juni State's Victory Award winner, 1993 April 23 (Box 3, Folder 120)
  - Gov. Weicker names Robert Plant to Office of Emergency Management post, 1993 April 26 (Box 3, Folder 121)
  - Claudia Weicker tells mothers, "Vaccinate - It’s the best shot your baby's got", 1993 April 27 (Box 3, Folder 122)
  - Memo to General Assembly regarding casino / slot machine legislation, 1993 April 28 (Box 3, Folder 123)
  - Robert F. Tessier named Deputy Labor Commissioner, 1993 April 29 (Box 3, Folder 124)
  - Gov. Weicker nominates Reginald Smith to Public Utilities Authority, 1993 April 30 (Box 3, Folder 125)
  - State, tribe sign amended agreement, Pequots to guarantee $113 million in payments, 1993 April 30 (Box 3, Folder 126)
  - Gov. Weicker nominates two new members to gaming policy board, 1993 May 3 (Box 3, Folder 127)
  - Veto message on death penalty, 1993 May 4 (Box 3, Folder 128)
  - Bills signed, 1993 May 4 (Box 3, Folder 129)
  - Letter to General Assembly with casino editorials, 1993 May 5 (Box 3, Folder 130)
  - Bills signed, 1993 May 5 (Box 3, Folder 131)
  - Memo to General Assembly, 'the mirage vs. the reality", 1993 May 7 (Box 3, Folder 132)
  - Dun & Bradstreet relocates headquarters to Connecticut, 1993 May 10 (Box 3, Folder 133)
  - Bills signed, 1993 May 10 (Box 3, Folder 134)
  - Gov. Weicker testimony to Base Realignment Commission, 1993 May 11 (Box 3, Folder 135)
  - Bills signed, 1993 May 12 (Box 3, Folder 136)
  - Gov. Weicker announces first issuing of December storm funds to towns, 1993 May 17 (Box 3, Folder 137)
  - Bills signed, 1993 May 19 (Box 3, Folder 138)
  - Bills signed and bills vetoed, 1993 May 20 (Box 3, Folder 139)
  - Veto message S.H.B. 7198 grievance procedures, 1993 May 20 (Box 3, Folder 140)
  - Gov. Weicker statement regarding gambling, 1993 May 21 (Box 3, Folder 141)
  - Bills signed, 1993 May 28 (Box 3, Folder 142)
  - Bond Commission meeting press releases, 1993 May 28 (Box 3, Folder 143)
  - Bills signed, 1993 June 2 (Box 3, Folder 144)
  - Bills signed, 1993 June 3 (Box 3, Folder 145)
  - Bills signed, 1993 June 4 (Box 3, Folder 146)
  - State reaches agreement with Pratt & Whitney on saving jobs, tax credits, job training part of package, 1993 June 4 (Box 3, Folder 147)
  - UPS press release, 1993 June 4 (Box 3, Folder 148)
  - Gov. Weicker seeks advisory opinion from Ethics Commission, 1993 June 7 (Box 3, Folder 149)
  - Veto S.B. 6964 sprinkler systems, 1993 June 7 (Box 3, Folder 150)
  - Bills signed, assault weapon, 1993 June 8 (Box 3, Folder 151)
  - Bills signed, 1993 June 8 (Box 3, Folder 152)
  - Gov. Weicker closing remarks for legislative session, 1993 June 9 (Box 3, Folder 153)
  - Bill signed, motor vehicle emissions, 1993 June 9 (Box 3, Folder 154)
  - Bill signed, 1993 June 10 (Box 3, Folder 155)
  - Bills signed, 1993 June 11 (Box 3, Folder 156)
  - Gov. Weicker speech at Brunswick School, 1993 June 11 (Box 3, Folder 157)
  - Bills signed and vetoed, 1993 June 14 (Box 3, Folder 158)
  - Gov. Weicker signs 1993 legislation to boost business climate, provide jobs, 1993 June 14 (Box 3, Folder 159)
  - Witco Corp. to consolidate headquarters, 800 jobs in Connecticut, 1993 June 15 (Box 3, Folder 160)
  - Gov. Weicker announces release of emergency snow removal funds to 83 cities and towns to offset March blizzard costs, 1993 June 16 (Box 3, Folder 161)
  - State announces new expense reduction program, 1993 June 17 (Box 3, Folder 162)
  - Bills signed, 1993 June 23 (Box 3, Folder 163)
  - Bills signed, 1993 June 23 (Box 3, Folder 164)
  - Press release, unemployment insurance bill signing, 1993 June 23 (Box 3, Folder 165)
  - Gov. Weicker names Jewett City receiver, taps former New London manager for post, 1993 June 23 (Box 3, Folder 166)
  - Gov. Weicker names John B. Meskill to lead Division of Special Revenue, 1993 June 24 (Box 3, Folder 167)
  - Statement about Rep. Donald J. Davino, 1993 June 24 (Box 3, Folder 168)
  - Statement, International Association of Machinists, 1993 June 24 (Box 3, Folder 169)
  - Press releases, Bond Commission meeting, 1993 June 25 (Box 3, Folder 170)
  - Press release, summer youth initiative, 1993 June 25 (Box 3, Folder 171)
  - Statement on sub base vote, 1993 June 25 (Box 3, Folder 172)
  - Press release, Dept. of Transportation (DOT) building, 1993 June 25 (Box 3, Folder 173)
  - Press release, school diversity bill signing, 1993 June 28 (Box 3, Folder 174)
  - Press release, reorganization bill signing, 1993 June 28 (Box 3, Folder 175)
  - Bills signed AM, 1993 June 28 (Box 3, Folder 176)
  - Bills signed PM, 1993 June 28 (Box 3, Folder 177)
  - Bills signed, 1993 June 29 (Box 3, Folder 178)
  - Bills signed, 1993 June 30 (Box 3, Folder 179)
  - Bills signed, 1993 June 30 (Box 3, Folder 180)
  - Terence Marloni named General Counsel, 1993 July 1 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Bills signed, 1993 July 1 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Bills signed, including message on auto insurance, 1993 July 1 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Veto, voir dire, 1993 July 2 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Veto, Medigap, 1993 July 2 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Veto, Motor vehicle dealerships, 1993 July 2 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Veto, campaign finance disclosure, 1993 July 2 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Message, parole bill, 1993 July 2 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Bills signed, 1993 July 2 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Writ of election, Donald J. Davino, 1993 July 2 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - R. Michael Dunne named as Commissioner of Dept. of Administrative Services, 1993 July 8 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Call for special session regarding bond authorizations, 1993 July 8 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Gov. Weicker nominates two to Workers' Compensation Commission, 1993 July 9 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Gov. Weicker names four to University of Connecticut Board of Trustees, 1993 July 10 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Gov. Weicker nominates Christine Keller and Jon Alander to Superior Court, 1993 July 15 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Connecticut closes year with balanced budget, Gov. Weicker announces surplus of more than $76 million, 1993 July 15 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Reward letter in connection with murders of Gregory Burke Hodge and David DeGregario, 1993 July 15 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Gov. Weicker names Sean C. Butterly as Claims Commissioner, 1993 July 16 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Bill signing, 1993 July 16 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Gov. Weicker names new members to State University and Community-Technical Colleges Boards of Trustees, 1993 July 23 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Press releases distributed at Bond Commission meeting, 1993 July 23 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Gov. Weicker names Stanley J. Kosloskias as Americans with Disabilities Act (ADA) coordinator, 1993 July 24 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Statement of Gov. Weicker on cigarette contraband, 1993 July 28 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Sen. Larson statement on Colonial Realty, 1993 July 29 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Gov. Weicker presents scholarships by the Disabled Worker Committee, 1993 August 12 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Storm emergency funds II press release, 1993 August 17 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Reward letter for murder of Jeannette Grice, 1993 August 20 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Mary B. Paulsen, 1905-1993, 1993 August 24 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Bond Commission meeting press releases, 1993 August 27 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Future direction of Civic Center, Hartford Whalers set, landmark lease and management agreements signed by Connecticut Development Authority, 1993 September 1 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Special session, 1993 September 3 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Grants to cities and communities for new officers and drug enforcement, 1993 September 4 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Gov. Weicker announces appointment of Rehabilitation Advisory Council, 1993 September 8 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Gov. Weicker statement on gang violence, State Police assisting Hartford Police Dept., 1993 September 8 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Gov. Weicker, Commissioner Scherer announce small cities grants of $7 million to 17 communities, 1993 September 9 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Dept. of Public Utility and Control (DPUC) report, 1993 September 15 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Indoor/outdoor amphitheater first of kind proposed for Hartford's North Meadows, 1993 September 15 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Special election November 2, 1993 for Juan Figueroa and Jonathan Pelo vacancies, 1993 September 17 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Copies of draft bill no. 8501, stadium, undated (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Gov. Weicker announces nominations of three new Superior Court judges, 1993 September 20 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Memorandum of understanding, State of Connecticut and New England Patriots, 1993 September 20 (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Briefing paper, relocation of the New England Patriots to Connecticut, relocation process, financing and control, 1993 September 21 (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - Briefing paper, relocation of the New England Patriots to Connecticut, 1993 September 21 (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - Bill signed, financing a stadium project, 1993 September 28 (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - Commodity Economic Development Fund Foundation Board's first meeting, 1993 September 29 (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - Gov. Weicker announces creation of Community Development Fund, Urbank II, for business in Connecticut cities, 1993 September 29 (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - Gov. Weicker statement on re-election 1994, 1993 September 30 (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - Gov. Weicker statement on Richard Levin, 1993 October 2 (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - Heather Hunt named to Development of Public Utility and Control (DPUC) Authority, 1993 October 8 (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - Reward letters, 1993 October 12 (Box 4, Folder 50)
  - Gov. Weicker's Care and Share Program 1993-1994 kick-off, 1993 October 13 (Box 4, Folder 51)
  - Letter to Secretary of the Navy John Dalton from Gov. Weicker, 1993 October 18 (Box 4, Folder 52)
  - Claudia Weicker and state garden officials unveil completed Wild Gardens Project at Governor's Residence, 1993 October 22 (Box 4, Folder 53)
  - Press Releases Bond Commission meeting, 1993 October 24 (Box 4, Folder 54)
  - Press Releases Bond Commission meeting, 1993 October 25 (Box 4, Folder 55)
  - Gov. Weicker orders opening of Cybulski Prison in Somers to avoid release of inmates and ease prison overcrowding, 1993 October 27 (Box 4, Folder 56)
  - Tours of the Governor's Residence offer history lessons for students of all ages as the state marks 50th anniversary of purchase, 1993 November 3 (Box 4, Folder 57)
  - Reward letter for murder of Evelyn "Lisa" Betancourt, 1993 November 4 (Box 4, Folder 58)
  - Gov. Weicker nominates Kevin Tierney to Superior Court, 1993 November 5 (Box 4, Folder 59)
  - Judge E. Eugene Spear nominated to Connecticut Appellate Court, 1993 November 5 (Box 4, Folder 60)
  - Special session of October bills and statement from Governor, 1993 November 12 (Box 4, Folder 61)
  - Allan Crystal to step down as Revenue Services Commissioner, 1993 November 15 (Box 4, Folder 62)
  - Bridgeport and New Haven to share $96 million grant to provide services to homeless mentally ill persons, 1993 November 17 (Box 4, Folder 63)
  - Gov. Weicker statement on Greater Bridgeport Mental Health Center, 1993 November 17 (Box 4, Folder 64)
  - Extradition papers for Janet Griffin, 1993 November 19 (Box 4, Folder 65)
  - Jan Kaplan named new director of Governor's Washington Office, 1993 November 19 (Box 4, Folder 66)
  - Mashantucket Pequot chairman Richard Hayward, Gov. Weicker announce $2 million donation to 1995 Special Olympics, 1993 November 30 (Box 4, Folder 67)
  - Reward letter for murder of Mark A. Salamon, 1993 December 1 (Box 4, Folder 68)
  - Katherine Carver appointed as Director of Commission on Deaf and Hearing Impaired, 1993 December 3 (Box 4, Folder 69)
  - Gov. Weicker authorizes reward seeking arrest in West Hartford bias case, 1993 December 3 (Box 4, Folder 70)